kluje.com 2019-05-23

# Privacy Policy | Kluje

Terms used but not defined in this [Privacy Policy](https://kluje.com/en/legal/privacy-policy) have the meaning given in the [User Agreement](https://kluje.com/en/legal/user-agreement).

Management and collection of personal data by the Website is subject to the Singapore Personal Data Protection Act (No. 26 of 2012) (the “ **Act** ”).  In this _[Privacy Policy](https://kluje.com/en/legal/privacy-policy)_ , “Personal Data” refers to any data, whether true or not, about an individual who can be identified (a) from that data; or (b) from that data and other information to which the Website has or are likely to have access, including data in the Website’s records as may be updated from time to time. 

In this policy the Website explains how it handles information about Members that the Website gathers, stores and uses. By accessing the Website each Member agrees and consents to the Website (including its related corporations and business entities) collecting, using and disclosing Personal Data in the manner set forth in this _[Privacy Policy](https://kluje.com/en/legal/privacy-policy)_. For additional information about Member’s relationship with the Website, please review the [User Agreement](https://kluje.com/en/legal/user-agreement).

## 1  Use of Member's Information

a.     The Website collects information about a Member through that Member’s use of the Services and the Website, including the registration details and information relating to a Members use of the Website and the Services (such as the content such Member accesses). 

b.     The Website uses the information it collects to help advertise to a Member, to verify a Member’s identity, to enforce or apply the Terms and Conditions, to protect the rights, property, or safety of the Website, Members, or others, for internal research purposes, for promoting and marketing the Website or content or partners of the Website. 

c.      The Website will release Personal Data only when it believes such release is appropriate for legal compliance and law enforcement (including to government agencies with statutory law enforcement responsibilities); to facilitate court proceedings; enforce or apply the Terms and Conditions; or protect the rights, property, or safety of the Website, Members, or others; or in accordance with Clause 1 (d) and / or (e). 

d.     Where the Website uses third parties to undertake services, it may provide those third parties with some of a Members’ information if it is required to fulfil those services. 

e.     Where permitted under the Act and subject to the provisions of any applicable regulations, a Members Personal Data may be disclosed to any third party service provider (in all cases in connection with a Service or with promotions or services provided by the Website or its related companies). 

## 2  Membership Registration

The Website registration form requires a Member to provide contact information and may also require demographic information. The Website may use the information from the registration form to send Member’s promotional material from the Website or some of its affiliated partners. A Member’s contact information is also used to contact that Member when necessary. 

## 3  Managing Personal Data

a.     The Act gives a Member the right to access and correct their information. A Member may contact the Website if they wish to access or update their information, including changing their email address, password, phone number, etc. When a Member updates their details the Website may store Member’s old details to ensure compliance with the Terms and Conditions. 

b.     If a Member wishes to close their account and delete any Personal Data that Member has submitted to the Website, they should contact the Website to make that request. 

## 4  Credit Card Security

The Website will take all reasonable steps to protect the security of a Member’s information, including credit and debit card information. 

## 5  Cookies

a.     The Website may use various technologies, including cookies and local storage, to collect and store information about Members when they visit the Website. 

b.     Cookies and local storage allow the Website to store information (including a Members Personal Data) in a file on the device a Member uses to access the Website. The Website may use cookies and local storage to deliver information and fresh content specific to a Member’s interests and to improve the experience of using the Website. 

c.      The Website may participate in Google's AdWords pay-per-click advertising programme. AdWords advertisements appear on Google's search result pages and on the Google Display Network. Website ads may also appear on other websites in the Google Display Network. Google uses cookies to target ads to a Member, including to measure the number of Google Members that click on certain advertisements and visit certain Website pages. 

d.     The Website may use Google remarketing to serve relevant ads to Members after they leave the Website. When a Member visits pages on the Website, the Website uses Google to place a cookie on a Member’s browser. Then when the Member later visits other websites in the Google Display Network, they may see ads from Trade Me because of that cookie. 

## 6  Advertising

a.     The Website endorses no service advertised on the Website. 

b.     The Website has no control over its advertisers' _[Privacy Policies](http://kluje.com/en/legal/privacy-policy)_ , and a Member should review such policies prior to submitting any information to them. 

c.      The Website may also use information it holds about a Member to deliver or display advertisements intended to be relevant to that Member’s interests, based on the information that a Member has provided to the Website through the use of any of the Services. 

## 7  Other Information Collected 

a.     The Website may use additional information to do internal research on Member’s demographics, interests, and behaviour to better understand Members. This information may include the URL that a Member just came from (whether this URL is on the Website or not), which URL that Member next goes to (whether this URL is on the Website or not), what device, operating system and browser a Member is using, and a Members IP address. The Website may also use information from third parties, such as geo-demographic information. 

b.     If a Member sends the Website personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other Members or third parties send the Website correspondence about a Member’s activities, the Website may collect such information into a file specific to a Member. 

c.      When Third Parties supply the Website with information in line with their terms and conditions, the Website may use this information to serve Member’s with more relevant advertising content. 

## 8  Membership Removal

       If a Member wishes to have their registration removed from the Website’s directory for any reason, they may send the Website an email requesting this. 

## 9  Updates to Information Practices

From time to time, the Website may make changes to its information practices (including this _[Privacy Policy](https://kluje.com/en/legal/privacy-policy)_ _)_ or alter the functionality of the Website.  

This _[Privacy Policy](https://kluje.com/en/legal/privacy-policy) _supplements but does not supersede nor replace any other consents or agreements a Member may have entered into with the Website.
